You must have heard about unlimited buffet and unlimited food.
In this policy, I will tell you how to get unlimited no-claim
bonus and unlimited claims. Yes,
I am talking
about the ICICI Lord Elevate policy. This
policy will give you unlimited claims as well as
unlimited no-claim bonus.
Before moving ahead, like this video and
subscribe to my channel so that
I can review all the policies in this way
and keep giving you interesting knowledge.
Now let's see what are the co-pay
benefits in this. Point number one: There is
room availability only up to a single private AC room,
but if you take a rider,
you can claim any room.
We will explain this rider more clearly in the next video.
Point number two: No co-pay. There is
no co-payment in this, which
means the company will settle the entire claim for you.
You do not need to pay even a single rupee from your pocket.
Point number three: No
supplements. There are no supplements of any kind in this, which
means even the smallest one.  You will get
up to two sum shots for even the most serious illness.
Point number four: Unlimited number of
restorations. It has unlimited number of
restorations. But one drawback here is
that you will be covered for the same person, same illness
only after 45 days. So if you are
taking this policy, then go for a higher sum inshot
so that this thing does not trigger you.
Point number five: No claim bonus: There is a
no claim bonus of 20% in this policy. This is
inbuilt, but if you take a rider, then there will be
unlimited no claim bonus. We will
see which rider is this in the next video. Point number
six: Pre and post hospitalization: This
policy has 90 days pre and 180 days
post. This is the only policy in which pre
hospitalization is of 90 days, whereas
in all other policies it is of only 60 days.
Point number seven: Day procedures are also
fully covered in this. What is a day procedure,
for which
you do not need to be admitted for 24 hours,
in two-three hours.  You will be treated with robotic surgery, all those
things are also
covered for you. All day treatments are
covered in the policy. Point number at
consumer benefit cover is in this policy.
Consumer
treatments are also covered in the policy. AYUSH
means Ayurvedic, Unani, Yudh Siddha,
Homeopathy means alternative treatment.
Ayurvedic treatment is also covered but it should be done
from a government recognized hospital only.
All these are comprehensive benefits
which are inbuilt in the policy. Now let us see
from which section on taking riders, benefits will be
added and from which section you should take rider.
Total 16 riders are available
in this policy. Let us decide one by
one. Rider number one: If you are
looking to take room type modification, then it is
my personal recommendation that you should definitely
consider this rider. Rider
number two and the most unique benefit is power
booster, which means your unlimited no claim bonus. If
you take a policy of Rs 10 lakh, then every year this Rs
10 lakh will double.  30 40 50 60 70 80 90
1 crore 2 crore 3 crore means
at the age of 30 if I am taking this rider
then after 30 years the value of this policy of ₹ 1 lakh will become
₹ crore so this
rider is replacing your super top up policy
now you do not need any super top up policy
rider number three
claim protector what does claim protector mean
it covers all your non consumable
items so if you are
looking to buy a policy then claim
protector rider is also a must rider number
four info care example if today
I am taking a policy of ₹ 10 lakh after 0
years this 10 lakh will become 30 lakh if ​​we
see that if I have taken this rider in the fourth year then in the
fourth year if my
claim comes for 50 lakh then the entire 50
lakh will be covered this rider means that
once in your life
You can claim any amount respecting your sum insured,
meaning if the value of your sum insured
is only 50 lakhs and your single sum
comes to one crore, then the entire one crore will be
given to you Rider number five Jump start
Jump start means this ABCD means
asthma, blood pressure, cholesterol, diabetes
If someone has any of these four diseases, then if he
takes this rider, he will be covered from day one There will be
no waiting period of three years for pre-existing, you will have to survive Everything will be
covered after 30 days of
taking the policy Rider number six
Dependent Accommodation It means that
if you are hospitalized for more than three days,
it has a criteria More than three days
If you are hospitalized for more than three days, then the person who
stays in the hospital with the patient will get Rs.
1 per day as a dependent accommodation Rider number seven
Compassionate visit means if someone is
coming to visit you and you are hospitalized for more than three days, then the maximum
he will get  The
company will give a claim up to ₹2000000
Whatever your travelling expenses are, the
company will cover them all. Maximum
limit to be 2000000 Rider number at
Domestic Air Ambulance Air Ambulance means
let's take an example if you are in Mumbai
and you have to
go to Delhi for some treatment, then that air ambulance will also be covered
if you take this rider. Point
number nine Personal Accident If you
take this rider and there is death through an accident, then
your nominee will
get the entire sum insured. In a
way, it works like term insurance
but only for accidental purpose. Rider
number 10 Network Advantage
What does Network Advantage mean? If you
take this rider, then you will get a discount of up to 10% on the entire premium.
But then if you have to make
any claim, then you have to
go only to a network hospital. If you do
not go to a network hospital or
go to a hospital which is not in the network, then
you will have to pay a copayment of 10%.
Avoid these riders, do not take these riders at all
to reduce your premium. Rider No. 11
Inflation Protector Inflation protector
means that let's take an example, today the
inflation rate of India is 7, so your
sum insured will increase by 7 every
year as your inflation rate increases
accordingly, that is, we are taking a policy of 10 lakhs
this year and this year your
inflation rate of India
is 7, inflation means inflation rate, if your
inflation rate of India is 7, then next
year the value of the policy will be 10 lakhs, there will
be 70000 increments and its
total value will become 10700, but there is
no need to take this rider because we are having
a power booster ride. Rider No.
12 Teleconsultation Teleconsultation means you
can take unlimited teleconsultation
with the doctor that I have this problem, please
tell me the solution, what medicine should I take
What should not be taken, then that is tele
consultation in unlimited time, if you
take this rider then rider number 13 critical illness,
if you take the rider of critical illness then
if you take the rider of critical illness, then if you are diagnosed with a critical illness
like cancer or heart attack, then your
nominee will get the entire sum insured, in a
way it
works like your term plan, there is no need to take this rider also,
now let's talk about the last rider, that is
B Fat Rider B Fat Rider,
this is a type of OPD rider, if you
take this rider then you will get three OPDs in it, there
is an option of up to A B CDs, if you take the G G
rider then you will get three OPDs for free, there is
no need to consider this rider also, so in this video I have taken a
sum insured of Rs 10 lakh, I have taken 30 years of
age and the premium of Jan Van,
what is the separate premium of all the riders, this will be visible to you on the screen, so
please consider all the riders once
and see which rider
is beneficial for you and  Which one is not, it is
not necessary to take all the riders,
I also do not recommend anyone to
take all the riders,
before taking any rider, you should confirm with your agent
whether this rider is necessary or not, if you
liked the video then like it, see you
in the next video